# **Niall Moone**

<u>Address:</u> Maddenstown Demesne, The Curragh, Co. Kildare

**Phone number:** 085-2844705

Email: n.moone@hotmail.com

**D.O.B.**: 16-03-1995

**LinkedIn:** https://ie.linkedin.com/in/niallmoone1995

# **Summary:**

I am a hard, working individual, studying computing in Tallaght IT and hoping to graduate in 2019. During my time in college, I have completed many continuous assessments and a few projects with a group, I have also worked in retail which has improved my skills such as communication and teamwork. I will also be available to work immediately if needed.

#### IT Skills

- Good knowledge with Java and C++.
- Able to design websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and play framework.
- Write SQL queries using Oracle 11g.
- Can use Windows, Linux and Ubuntu operating systems
- Can create and design database schemas
- Design and troubleshoot a network using routers.

### **Education and Qualifications**

# Patricians Brothers School - September 2008 - 2014

#### Leaving certificate

English (B); Maths (B); History (C); Design Communication Graphics (B); Construction studies (C); Geography (D); Link Modules (D)

# Institute of Technology Tallaght – 2014 - present Bachelor of Science Computing

**First Year Subjects,** Software Development 1(**B-**); Computer Architecture(**B**); Fundament of Interface & Web(**C+**); Business & Information Sys(**C**); Discrete Mathematics 1(**B-**); Learning to Learn 3<sup>rd</sup> IvI(**B**); Software Development 2(**C+**); Object Oriented System Analysis(**B-**); Social Media Communications(**B**); Statistics(**C**); Database Fundamentals(**B**); Operational System Fundamentals(**C**)

**Second Year Subjects,** Software Development 3(**C**); Software Quality Assurance & Testing(**C**); Networking 1(**D**); Database Design & Programming(**C**); Discrete Mathematics 2(**B**); Web Design and Development(**B**-); Software Development 4(**C**); Networking 2(**D**); Management Science(**B**-); Object Oriented Analysis & Design(**D**); Information Security(**C**)

# **College Projects**

#### **Java Program**

#### **Description**

A Second-Year group project consisting of three people, to design an application using either Play Framework or Java. Our application was a Recording Studio Management System which is designed to allow a user to log in, book a band, update booking, delete booking and search the database.

#### **Programs and Tools Used:**

NetBeans 8.1, Sql, Java, JavaFX, XML

# **Work History**

# Warehouse operative at LidI RDC

# <u>6.11.2017 - 17</u>.08.2018

- Move, pick and load all food types and non-food products
- Ensure stock is received, stored, packed and transported according to high standards
- Work in both ambient and temperature-controlled environments
- Maintain the uninterrupted flow of goods in and out of the regional distribution centres
- Always maintain strict food safety and health and safety standards.
- Keep the distribution centre clear and ensure any potential hazards are dealt with quickly and efficiently

#### Sales Assistant at Reebok Kildare Village

# 01.04.2013- 20.06.2013

- Processing large deliveries
- Assisting customers on the shop floor with customer service skills
- General housekeeping and cleanliness
- Stock replenishment

# Machine operator at MBQ Engineering

# 01.09.2014-2016

- Operating teleporter and other machinery
- · Ordering materials
- Office administrative duties

#### **Interests and Achievements**

Reading sci-fi and thriller novels in spare time, drawing and sketching, learning to animate, active member in Archery society, cooking.

- Winning the Best New Society award at the 2016 BICS Awards
- Winning college award for Best New Society
- Employee of the Month Reebok
- Received five Bronntar An Gradam Seo Ar awards in secondary school
- 2nd place of Cecil Day Lewis Literary Award 2010

#### Referees

Mr James Quinn

Director

MBQ Engineering

Nurney

Co. Kildare

Ashleigh Moone

Store Manager

Reebok Kildare Village

Kildare Town

Co. Kildare

 Co. Kildare
 Co. Kildare

 087 7445956
 087 9727257